Guide to the Rabinowitz, Boudin, Standard, Krinsky and Lieberman Legal Files TAM.287
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Legal Work and Client Files, 1915-1992
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Federal Television and Radio NLRB Petition, 1945-1946 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: General Electric, 1945 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: General Motors / NLRB, 1944-1946 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Lewyt Corporation, 1944-1945 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Los Angeles Shipbuilding and Drydock Corp., 1944-1945 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Midvale Company (NLRB Petitions), 1944-1946 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Otis Elevator Company Contract, 1944 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: RCA New Jersey Contract, 1945-1946 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Sharp, George (NLRB Petition), 1946 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - Federation of Architects, Engineers, Chemists and Technicians: Sigman, H. Irving and Madigan-Hyland Company, Ltd., 1945 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Airport Clearance Service, 1971 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Correspondence, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Correspondence, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Correspondence (I), 1968 (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Correspondence (II), 1968 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Florida Land Deals, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Forest, Jim - Theft of Auto, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Guttentag, Harry and Dora, 1968-1969 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Incorporation, 1964-1966 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Pension Plan, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Skyview Acres Cooperative, Inc., 1968 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Tax Exempt Status (I), 1959-1964 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Tax Exempt Status (II), 1959-1964 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Tax Exempt Status - Ashbrook, Forest, et al. v. Village of Upper Nyack, 1962-1966 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Various Statements, Minutes, Press Releases, Memoranda, Notes and Publications, 1957-1972 (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Various Statements, Minutes, Press Releases, Memoranda, Notes and Publications (I), 1960-1970 (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Various Statements, Minutes, Press Releases, Memoranda, Notes and Publications (II), 1960-1970 (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation: Various Statements, Minutes, Press Releases, Memoranda, Notes and Publications, 1961-1966, Undated (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Friedman Conference of the Columbia Society of International Law: Letter, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Gelbart, Abe: Academic Freedom and Tenure, Communist Party, 1953-1954 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Glasser, Abraham: Academic Freedom, HUAC (I), 1941-1953 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Glasser, Abraham: Academic Freedom, HUAC (II), 1941-1953 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Gore, Earl M., Sayre and Lazar v. Joseph F. Farley, Commandant of the U.S. Coast Guard: Communist Party Membership, 1949 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Heimlich, Simon W.: Academic Freedom, McCarran Committee, 1951-1953 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - International Association of Democratic Lawyers (IADL) Conference, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - IADL Conference: Materials, 1960-1964 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT)/ American Communications Association (ACA)/ Communication Workers of America (CWA): People of the State of New York v. Henry Habel, Arthur McGovern, Kenneth Burkard, Julio Rodriguez and Morgan Seifert-Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - IBT/ACA/CWA: New York v. Henry Habel, et al.- Exhibits, 1963-1965 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - IBT/ACA/CWA: New York v. Henry Habel, et al.- Formal (I), 1964-1967 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - IBT/ACA/CWA: New York v. Henry Habel, et al.- Formal (II), 1964-1967 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - IBT/ACA/CWA: New York v. Henry Habel, et al.-Various Case-Related Materials, 1964-1966 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - IBT, Local 840: Deutsch, Frederick, et al. v. Jeanne Kaplan, 1973-1977 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - IBT, Local 840: Deutsch, Frederick, et al. v. Jeanne Kaplan, 1975-1976 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), Local 14-14B: Gates, Leroy v. Ralph Dalton, et al. -- Correspondence, 1973-1979 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Court Documents, 1973-1977 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Court Documents, 1974-1978 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Court Documents, 1978-1980 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Court Documents, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Documents re: Class Notice, [1973]-[1980] (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Documents re: Reimbursements, 1978 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Negotiations and Disbursements, 1973-1980 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - IUOE, Local 14-14B: Gates v. Dalton- Notes, Drafts, Memoranda, [1973]-[1980] (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Krebs, Allen M. v. John M. Ashbrook et al.(HUAC): Amicus Curiae (Emergency Civil Liberties Committee), 1966 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Lewis, Stuart, M.D., 1981 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - McDonald, Larry: Articles re Socialist Workers Party, 1975-1977 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Margolis, Harry: Rosenthal Committee Hearings, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET): Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - NABET: Agreements, Constitution and By-Laws, 1967-1973 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - NABET: News and Views, Local 11, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - NABET: Suspension of 17 Employees (NBC) Arbitration, 1970-1971 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - NABET: Various Arbitrations, 1967-1971 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Needleman and Needleman v. Secretary of State: Passports (Notes), [1964] (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - New Action Coalition: New Action Coalition v. United Federation of Teachers (UFT), Local 2- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - New Action Coalition: New Action Coalition v. UFT, Local 2- Formal, 1981-1982 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - New Action Coalition: New Action Coalition v. UFT, Local 2- Notes and Memos, [1981] (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - New Action Coalition: New Action Coalition v. UFT, Local 2- Research, 1973-1980 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - New Action Coalition: New Action Coalition v. UFT, Local 2- UFT Elections, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - New York Central Railroad Company: National Mediation Board Findings re Employee Representation, 1941 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - New York City Department of Hospitals, Local 420 (AFSCME, DC 37): Bonano, et al. v. Butler, et al.(Rabinowitz, Neutral Observer), 1979-1981 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - New York City Department of Hospitals, Local 420: Bonano v. Butler- AFSCME Material, 1978, Undated (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - New York City Department of Hospitals, Local 420: Bonano v. Butler- Formal, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Nichols, Russell: Uniformed Court Officers Association, Local 598, SEIU - Grievance (I), 1975-1979 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Nichols, Russell: Uniformed Court Officers Association, Local 598, SEIU - Grievance (II), 1975-1979 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Nuclear Power, 1977, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining, New York City, 1968-1975 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Office of Collective Bargaining, New York City, 1977-1981 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Operation PUSH (People United to Save Humanity), 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Otto, Nathan: Passport (Notes), 1954 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Park, Willard Zerbe v. John Foster Dulles: Passport, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Partico Socialista Puertorriqueno (PSP): FOIA/COINTELPRO, 1970s (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Progressive Labor Anti-Kennedy, Military Industrial Complex: Articles and Flyer, Undated (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Protestants and Others United for the Separation of Church and State, 1966-1967 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Protestants and Others United for the Separation of Church and State: Allendorfer, Maurice, et al. v. Human Resources Corporation, et al., 1965-1966 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Rabinowitz, L. M. and Company, Inc.: Trust Agreements and Jack B. Mendelsohn Pension Trust Documents, 1957-1958 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Contribution to The Politics of Law, A Progressive Critique edited by David Kairys, 1988-1989 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Contribution to The Politics of Law, A Progressive Critique edited by David Kairys, 1990-1992 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Correspondence re: Library for Marxist Studies, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Objections to Questions on Bar Admission Application, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Racial Discrimination and Tax Exempt Status: Various Cases, 1972 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Reinhardt v. National Council of Marine Draftsmen, Inc., 1944 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, CIO (I), 1949 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, CIO (II), 1949 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, CIO (III), 1949 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Retail, Wholesale and Department Store Union, Local 1250: Douds, Charles (NLRB) v. Local 1250, 1948-1949 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Rosenberg, Arthur R. et al. v. James E. Allen, Jr. et al.: Anti-War Activity, Discharge of Teacher, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Rosinger, Lawrence: Senate Subcommittee on Internal Security (McCarran Committee), 1951-1954 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Rothenburg, Morris: Denial of Classified Clearance, 1954 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Salzman, Sam: Coast Guard Screening Interrogatories, 1957 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Schneider, Herman and Nina: Sale of Property, 1952-1953 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Seton Hall University: University Faculty, 1975 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Smith Act Trials (I), 1949-1950 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Smith Act Trials (II), 1949-1950 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Alice: Auto Accident, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Socialist Party Program: Draft Paper (no author identified), 1956 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Socialist Workers Party: Requests for Equal Broadcast Time, 1975-1976 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Stephens, Bifford: Employment Controversy, 1978 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Subversive Activities Control Board, 1962 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Survey of State Sedition Statutes, 1964, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Teachers Union: Appeal of Barnofsky, Danielowitz, Grossman, Kurzman, 1955 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Teachers Union: Appeal of Kurzman, Maurice - Dismissal (I), 1953-1958 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Teachers Union: Appeal of Kurzman, Maurice - Dismissal (II), 1953-1958 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Citron, Alice, et al., 1950-1974 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Citron, et al., 1968-1972, Undated (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Citron, et al. - Formal, 1967-1968 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Grossman, Mildred, et al. - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Grossman, et al. - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Grossman, et al. - Formal, 1972-1973 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Grossman, et al. - Record of Dismissals, 1951-1955 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Grossman, et al. - Research, Related Cases, 1972-1973 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Nash, Julius and Maurer, Irving, 1962-1971 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Nash and Maurer, 1963-1964 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Nash, Julius; Maurer, Irving; Feinstein, Minerva and Adler, Harry, 1943-1962 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Nash, Maurer, et al., 1944-1945, 1955-1962 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Nash, Maurer, et al., 1954-1972 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Nash, Maurer, et al., 1955-1964 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Nash, Maurer, et al., 1960 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Nash, Maurer, et al., 1962-1964 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Seltzer, Morris; Case, Meyer; Cohen, Lewis, et al., 1968-1973 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Straus, Dudley, 1937, 1967-1983 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Straus, Dudley, 1954-1982 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Teachers Union: Application of Straus, Dudley, 1973-1982 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. James E. Allen, Adler, Nash, Feinstein, Maurer and Cohen, 1954-1963 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al.(I), 1955-1959 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al.(II), 1955-1959 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al., 1955-1960 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al., 1955-1961, Undated (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al., 1956-1958 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al., 1956-1960 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al., 1958-1961 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al., 1960 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al.- Press, 1954-1963 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al.- Special Hearing, 1962 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed v. Allen, et al. and Associated Claims, 1953, 1955, 1960-1961 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Teachers Union: Board of Ed and Jansen, William v. Allen, Adler, Nash, Feinstein, Maurer and Cohen- Related Materials, 1952-1955 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Teachers Union: Charges of Board of Ed against Skovron, Morris J., 1932-1954 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Teachers Union: Charges of Board of Higher Ed against Austin, Warren, 1957-1959 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Teachers Union: Correspondence and Billing, 1955-1964 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Teachers Union: Elections, 1961 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Teachers Union: Elections (I), 1961-1962 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Teachers Union: Elections (II), 1961-1962 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Teachers Union: Feinberg Law, Various Documents, 1967-1973 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Teachers Union: General, 1949-1954 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Teachers Union: Jansen, William v. Henry Danielowitz, 1953 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Teachers Union: Jansen, William v. Henry Danielowitz and Subsequent Appeal, 1953-1954 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Teachers Union: Jansen, William v. Mildred Flacks, 1952 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Teachers Union: Jansen, William v. Julius Lemansky, 1952-1953 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Teachers Union: Jansen, William v. Squire, Eliashow, Hirschfield, Auerbach, Barnof sky, Danielowitz, Eckstat, London and Kurzman, 1936-1955 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Teachers Union: Jansen, William v. Squire, et al., 1950-1953 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Teachers Union: Jansen, William v. Squire, et al., 1951-1955 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Textile Workers Union (Dyers): Lavis Mills Corporation v. Federation of Dyers, Finishers, Printers and Bleachers of America, et al.; Textile Workers Union of America, CIO; Emil Rieve, et al., [1946] (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Thorstad, David: Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Appeal (I), 1967-1978 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Thorstad, David: FOIA Appeal (II), 1967-1978 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Transport Workers Union (TWU): Lewis, Henry v. NYC Transit Authority- Briefs, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - TWU: Lewis v. NYC Transit Authority- Formal, 1979-1983 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - TWU: Lewis v. NYC Transit Authority- Research, 1978-1979, Undated (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Barry, Mary Jane, et al. Grievance/ Contract Dispute, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Bradley, Arlene, 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Bulletin Board Issue, 1982-1983 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Bulletin Board Issue, Briefs, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Bulletin Board Issue (Currier, Nancy), 1983 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute, Briefs, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute, Exhibits, 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute (Fink, Patricia), 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute, General, 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute (Kartis, Diane), 1979-1982 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute (Lord, Robin), 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute (O'Such, Bruce), 1982 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute (Paluch, James), 1981-1982 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Document 26 Dispute, Ready Reserves, 1982 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Eccles, Dale, 1974-1975 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Fink, Patricia, 1968-1981 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - "No Work No Pay" Grievances, 1973-1982 (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - "No Work No Pay" Grievances, 1978-1982 (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Search Grievance, 1973-1981 (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Search Grievance, Exhibits, 1980-1981 (Box 99, Folder 26)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Search Grievance (Matchett, Susan), 1974-1980 (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Search Grievance (Simmons, Sally) Audio Tape Included, 1975-1980 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Transcon Arbitration, 1980-1981, Undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Various Arbitration and Grievance Exhibits, 1962-1983 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - TWU, Local 553: Eastern Airlines - Various Arbitration and Grievance Exhibits, 1967, 1970, 1980-1981 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs, May 28, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs (I), Jun 30, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs (II), Jun 30, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs, Jul 9, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs, Jul 20, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs, Aug 27, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs, Sep 1982-Oct 1982 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs (I), Nov 29, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs (II), Nov 29, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs (III), Nov 29, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs, Dec 27, 1982 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs, Sep 1983 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - TWU, Local 553: TWU v. Eastern Airlines- Briefs, Oct 1983 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Uniformed Sanitation Men Association (USMA): USMA v. Commissioner of Sanitation of the City of New York- Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - USMA: USMA v. Commissioner of Sanitation- Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - USMA: USMA v. Commissioner of Sanitation- Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - USMA: USMA v. Commissioner of Sanitation- Formal, 1966-1969 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - USMA: USMA v. Commissioner of Sanitation- Formal, 1967-1968 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - USMA: USMA v. Commissioner of Sanitation- Formal, 1968-1969 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - USMA: USMA v. Commissioner of Sanitation- Formal, 1969-1972 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - USMA: USMA v. Commissioner of Sanitation- Related Cases, 1966-1967 (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - United Black Workers, 1970-1974 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE): Fay, Charles as President of the Amalgamated Machine Instrument and Metal Local 475, UE v. Charles T. Douds (NLRB), [1948]-[1949] (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE): Various Cases, 1949-1954 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - United Furniture Workers of America (UFWA), Local 140, Bedding, Curtain and Drapery Workers Union, 1951-1968 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - UFWA, Local 140: ABC Mattress Company, 1953-1961 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Ace Fiber Mills, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Adler's Bed Spring Corporation, 1953-1955, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Allied Drapery Company, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Aristocrat Rest Products Corporation, 1956-1961 (Box 101, Folder 16)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Joseph Aronauer, Inc., 1963, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Associated Venetian Blind Manufacturers, 1954 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - UFWA, Local 140: AZ Venetian Blind Corporation, 1959-1960 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Arnold W. Becker & Co., Inc., 1956-1962 (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Belfer Brothers Company (Knickerbocker Feathers Corporation), 1953-1961 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Bilt-Rite Mattress Company, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Bond Bedding Company, 1954-1956 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Bonnie Manufacturing Company, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Bonnie Pillow Inc., 1960 (Box 101, Folder 25)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Bridgeport Bed Spring Company, 1965-1968 (Box 101, Folder 26)
  - UFWA, Local 140: L. Buchman & Company, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 27)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Capital Box Spring, Inc., 1957 (Box 101, Folder 28)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Center Mattress Company, 1959-1965 (Box 101, Folder 29)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Circle Imports, Inc., 1968 (Box 101, Folder 30)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Colavito v. Dorsey and People v. Carion- Handbill Distribution, 1965 (Box 101, Folder 31)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Compliance, 1950-1956 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Compliance, 1955-1959 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Continental Novelties, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - UFWA, Local 140: D&L Bedding Company, Inc., 1958, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - UFWA, Local 140: DeChamps, Joseph, 1965 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Eclipse Sleep Products, Inc., 1961, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - UFWA, Local 140: Eldine Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1961 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - UFWA, Local 140: The Englander Company, Inc., 1952 (Box 102, Folder 8)